

Raju Pratama Ritonga

Business Developement





Contact

Phone Number +6282276334163

Address

Jl. Kramat Raya No.7-9, RT.4/RW.2, Kramat Kec. Senen, Kota Jakarta Pusat Daerah Khusus Ibukota Jakarta 10450

E-mail

rajuritonga@gmail.com

Languages

Indonesia English



Skills

Software

- Microsoft Office
- Photoshop CS6



Public Speaking

Negoitation





About me Passionate marketer and business development who have a strong interest startup industry especially in the field fast moving consumer goods [FMCG] and ed-tech, a person who likes to share experiences and always to learn from anyone especially from great minds around me. Have a high sense of responsibility, and try to go beyond the boundaries to inspire others around. Skilled in presentation, design, event organizing, public speaking, and team management

Education

Primary School

SDN 114369 Sei Raja

Junior High School

MTsN 2 Rantau Prapat

Senior High School

SMAN 1 Rantau Utara

University

Bachelor of Agribusiness Universitas Sumatera Utara

Experience

Work November 2020 - Februari 2021

Business Development Intern Defuture Farmer

Work | April 2021 - May 2021

Education Consultant Ruang Guru

Work | May 2021 - July 2021

Regional Officer QERA Education Group

Work July - Now

Sales Development Representative Glints